Omaha Powwow Project collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 2: 1983 Omaha Tribal Powwow
  - Subseries 1: Carl Fleischhauer
    - Sub-subseries 2: Color photographs
      - Camera roll, August 14, 1983, AFC 1986/038: FCP/O-CF-13; 26 photographs: color transparencies; 35 mm (slide format) (Boxes 4, 6)
        7-14 Macy housing, generally north and northeast of the pow-wow grounds
        15-17 Apartment block in Macy
        18 (?) Community college
        19-20 Macy main street
      - Camera roll, August 14-15, 1983, AFC 1986/038: FCP/O-CF-14; 26 photographs: color transparencies; 35 mm (slide format); 8/14 (pow-wow) and 8/15 (landscape) (Boxes 4, 6)
        1-6 baseball game in Macy
        10-11 view of bluffs, Missouri River, and Iowa from hilltop where Dorothy Lee and I were chased by a raccoon
        12-13 view of Iowa from same spot
        14-15 Farm on Nebraska state highway 94, Thurston Co.
      - Camera roll, August 15, 1983, AFC 1986/038: FCP/O-CF-15; 15 photographs: color transparencies; 35 mm (slide format) (Boxes 4, 6)
        1-2 Missouri River valley and bluffs from sacred spot
        3-4 tree that looked like a buffalo or cow skull at the same place
        5-7 the clearing at that place (tree in background)
      - Color photo prints, August 12-14, 1983, 4 photographs: prints, color; various sizes (Box-folder 1/7)
  - Subseries 2: Dorothy Sara Lee
    Archivist's note: Lee's original documentation has been used to describe the photos, with minor edits for clarity.
    - Field notes, 1983, 53 pages (Box-folder 1/15)
    - Sub-subseries 1: Black-and-white photographs
      - Black-and-white photo logs, 1983, 12 pages (Box-folder 1/12)
      - Camera roll, August 12, 1983, AFC 1986/038: 214183-3; 36 photographs: film, negatives, black and white; 35 mm; Afternoon and evening (Box 2)
        1-3 Gayle Cable introducing Gourd Dance
        4-5 Drum group before Gourd Dance
        6-7 Roger Welsch
        8-12 Gourd Dance
        12-16 Children dressed for Pow-wow competition
        17-22 Gourd dancers
        23-31 Grand Entry, Friday evening
        32-34 Small child at flag song
        35 Clown
        36 CBS cameramen
      - Camera roll, August 13, 1983, AFC 1986/038: 214183-5; 37 photographs: film, negatives, black and white; 35 mm; Afternoon and evening (Box 2)
        1-3 Host drum
        4 Senior citizens
        5 Grand Entry, afternoon
        6 Whipman
        7-9 Traditional dancers
        10 Drum
        11-12 Child at end of dance line
        13-14 Whipman recognition dance
        15 Tail dancer
        16-19 Pow-wow Princess
        20-26 San Juan Pueblo group: Eagle Dance
        27-28 Carl Fleischhauer
        29-31 Tent, cars, and regalia on hill
        32-33 Grand Entry, evening; senior citizens
        34-37 Paul Brill special
      - Camera roll, August 13, 1983, AFC 1986/038: 214183-6; 33 photographs: film, negatives, black and white; 35 mm; Evening (Box 2)
        1-2 Paul Brill special
        3-4 Judges
        5-15 Paul Brill handing out genealogies; 2 sisters; Charlie Edwards; Joseph Harlan; Rufus White
        16-19 Reading genealogies in grandstand
        20-21 Clifford Wolfe
        22 Elmer Blackbird
        23-26 Clifford Wolfe reading genealogies
        27-28 More presentations
        29-30 Presentation to Dennis Hastings
        31-32 Junior Girl's Shawl competition; judging
      - Camera roll, August 13, 1983, AFC 1986/038: 214183-1; 35 photographs: film, negatives, black and white; 35 mm; Evening (Box 2)
        1-7 Junior Boy's Fancy Dance competition
        8-9 2 Junior Traditional contestants
        10-12 Contest judges
        13-15 Little Girl's Cloth competition
        16-20 Junior Girl's Cloth competition
        21 Little Boy's Traditional competition
        22-24 Junior Boy's Traditional competition
        25-31 General Dance
        32-34 San Juan group: Buffalo Dance
        35 General dance
      - Camera roll, August 13, 1983, AFC 1986/038: 215338-1; 18 photographs: film, negatives, black and white; 35 mm (Box 2)
        No frame description in the photo log.
      - Camera roll, August 13-14, 1983, AFC 1986/038: 214183-2; 35 photographs: film, negatives, black and white; 35 mm; Saturday evening/Sunday afternoon (Box 2)
        1-2 Special
        3-4 One of the singers listening to a recording made earlier [Sunday afternoon]
        5-6 Maria at entrance to her camper
        7 Drums and shed
        8 Nebraska ETV camera
        9 Clifford Wolfe
        10-12 Carl Fleischhauer and Drum group
        13-16 Grand Entry [Sunday afternoon]; Pow-wow Committee; Tiny Tots Traditional dancers; senior citizens
        17 Boys on bench
        18-28 San Juan group: Buffalo Dance
        29-35 Special for John Turner
      - Camera roll, August 14, 1983, AFC 1986/038: 214183-4; 35 photographs: film, negatives, black and white; 35 mm (Box 2)
        1-6 Special for John Turner; Kenny Blackbird with flute
        7-8 Paul Brill
        9 Child fixing claw-foot staff
        10-11 Paul Brill handing out more genealogies
        12 General dance
        13 Boy examining regalia
        14-16 Special for Blaine Mitchell
        17-27 San Juan group: young Buffalo dancer
        28-33 San Juan group: farewell
        34-35 Special
      - Black-and-white contact sheets, August 12-14, 1983, 7 photographs: contact sheets, black and white; approx. 8 1/2 in. x 11 in. (Box-folder 1/11)
    - Sub-subseries 2: Color photographs
      - Color photo logs, 1983, 6 pages (Box-folder 1/13)
      - Camera roll, August 12, 1983, AFC 1986/038: FCP/O-DSL-1; 8 photographs: color transparencies; 35 mm (slide format) (Box 4)
        1 Roger Welsch
        2 Young traditional dancer
        3-7 Grand entry, Friday evening; Whipman
        8 Whipman recognition dance
      - Camera roll, August 13, 1983, AFC 1986/038: FCP/O-DSL-2; 15 photographs: color transparencies; 35 mm (slide format); Afternoon (Box 4)
        1 Gourd dance
        2-7 Grand Entry, Saturday afternoon
        8-10 Melanie Parker, Pow-wow Princess: solo
        11-15 San Juan Pueblo Indian Youth Dancers: Eagle Dance
      - Camera roll, August 14, 1983, AFC 1986/038: FCP/O-DSL-3; 18 photographs: color transparencies; 35 mm (slide format); Afternoon (Box 4)
        1-3 Carl; drums and drummers
        4 One of the arena directors
        5 Rufus White, head singer
        6-14 Grand Entry; K. ft. Edwards L#8J; senior citizens
        15 David Blackbird, Whipman
        16-18 San Juan group: Buffalo Dance
      - Camera roll, August 14, 1983, AFC 1986/038: FCP/O-DSL-4; 18 photographs: color transparencies; 35 mm (slide format); Afternoon (Box 4)
        1-2 Conclusion of San Juan group Buffalo Dance
        3 Traditional Buckskin
        4-10 John Turner special
        11-12 Women's Cloth competition
        13-15 Women's Shawl competition
        16 Head Judge
        17-18 Fancy Dance judging
      - Camera roll, August 14, 1983, AFC 1986/038: FCP/O-DSL-5; 19 photographs: color transparencies; 35 mm (slide format); Afternoon (Box 4)
        1 Men's Fancy Dance competition; judging
        2-11 Men's Traditional competition; judging
        12-13 Blaine Mitchell special
        14-19 Youngest Buffalo dancer, San Juan group
      - Camera roll, probably 1983, AFC 1986/038: FCP/O-DSL-6; 19 photographs: color transparencies; 35 mm (slide format) (Box 4)
  - Subseries 3: Sound recordings
    Archivist's note: Dorothy Sara Lee's original documentation, when available, has been used to describe the recordings, with minor edits for clarity. See Box-Folders 1/14 and 1/15.
    - Audio logs, 1983, 31 pages (Box-folder 1/14)
    - Tape 1, August 13, 1983, AFC 1986/038: SR01; RXI 0234; 1 sound tape reel (00:32:42): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Contents
      Gourd Dance [1]
      Gourd Dance [2]
      Gourd Dance [3]
      Gourd Dance [4]
      Break (Ambulance Station; Carl "Hello Maria" announcements)
      Conclusion of Gourd Dance
      Announcement of Grand Entry
      National Anthem
    - Tape 2, August 13, 1983, AFC 1986/038: SR02; RXI 0235; 1 sound tape reel (00:32:15): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      4 Traditional War Songs
      Intertribals
      Hill Dance
      Announcement of Pow-Wow Committee
      Chairman Blackbird - speech
      David Blackbird - Whipman
      4 Tail Dancers
      Traditional War Dancers
      Pow-wow Princesses
    - Tape 3, August 13, 1983, AFC 1986/038: SR03; RXI 0236; 1 sound tape reel (00:32:05): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Tail section of Songs used to give honor to singers or drum groups.
      An extra mike was moved by a woman singer, and later was placed in front of the women.
      Dancing (with women's mike)
      Unknown number of songs
      Tribal Chairman Blackbird makes introductions
      Discusses visit by Gov. Kerry's brother, assistant to the brother, then Bill Carrey (Carey?)
      Then discussion of help from Sen. Exon [J. James Exon]
      Cites previous help with getting electrical power
      Bill Hopuer [sp?] and family [this is followed by an unclear note in Lee's handwriting: "no continue between #3 & 4"]
    - Tape 4, August 13, 1983, AFC 1986/038: SR04; RRXI 0237; 1 sound tape reel (00:32:17): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      End of Buffalo Dance from San Juan Pueblo
      War Dance (Intertribal)
      Speaker: Betty Logdon [sp?], Nebraska Historical Society
      San Juan Pueblo - Eagle Dance (continued on SR05. Lee notes: "switch mike - should be better on right")
    - Tape 5, August 13, 1983, AFC 1986/038: SR05; RXI 0238; 1 sound tape reel (00:32:11): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      San Juan Pueblo - Eagle Dance (continued from SR04 )
      Thomas Brothers - speech to crowd
      Rich and myself [sic - Dorothy Sara Lee] - speech to crowd
      Dorothy Sara Lee [?] - Traditional "Tail" Dance
      Another Intertribal
      Announcement looking for dinner for the "nursing" home
      "Clear the arena" announcement - Dorothy Lee and Band
      Maria plays tapes, dancers dance to recordings
      Loudspeaker with recording - left; Maria's voice - right. Continued on SR06.
    - Tape 6, August 13, 1983, AFC 1986/038: SR06; RXI 0239; 1 sound tape reel (00:32:15): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Maria and tapes
      Continued from SR05. Lee notes she may have lost 10-20 seconds of audio between reel changes.
      Maria's show ends with Columbia cylinder of flute songs
      Maria: on our plans for a record album
      Dorothy presents tapes to tribal chairman
      Next song (Drum #2 off mike)
      Speaker remarks on marathon
      Next song (Drum #1 - speaker says something about princess)
      Next song (Drum #1 - speaker names people - Pow-Wow Princess Special)
      Dance led by princess and older women
      Princess gives money
    - Tape 7 [not marked in audio log], August 13, 1983, AFC 1986/038: SR07; RXI 0240; 1 sound tape reel (00:32:21): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Remark: for princess's grandmother giveaway
      [?] giveaway by princess (at this point the tape was shut off for about half an hour, and turned on again for the announcements)
      Next song, honoring someone (for Louis Dick [Louis Dick, Sr.]); lead dancer may have been brother Albert Dick [Albert Dick, Sr.]
      "The Half Breed Song"
      Money given
      Siren
      Mr. Dick (is it Louis?) makes speech (of thanks?) in Omaha [language] (at this point there were more small giveaways and remarks, etc., which were not recorded)
      Recording restarted in time for the flag lowering song (Lee notes that "the action wiggled the flagpole; some electrical fizzing on our wire")
      Flag lowering followed by a song (the song title is noted on the tape)
      Announcements - supper, etc. (the recording is "cut for supper)
      Grand Entry (Eagle Bone) (continued on SR08 )
    - Tape 8, August 13, 1983, AFC 1986/038: SR08; RXI 0241; 1 sound tape reel (00:32:23): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Grand Entry (continued from SR07; tail end; about 30 seconds)
      Posting of "Colors" (Flag)
      Whipman's Song
      Committee Song
      Tail Dancers - four Traditional War Dance Songs ("Wakonda," the second song of four, is on cylinder, and was played earlier in the afternoon at the presentation. This set of four songs are original Helushka.)
      Song for Head Dancer - "Whipman (for David Blackbird)
      Song for Tail Dancers
      Introduction of Singers; Princess; Arena Directors; Water Boys, Pow-wow Committee
      "Honey Creek Singers" - Sneak Up Dance (a little off-mike)
    - Tape 9, August 13, 1983, AFC 1986/038: SR09; RXI 0242; 1 sound tape reel (00:30:36): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Tia Piah Singers
      Change in songs - medley
      Contesting
      Tiny Tots Shawl Contest (seven contestants; singers will sing two times through)
      Song #1 - warm-up by singers off to side
      Song #2 - contest song for Girls shawl
      Junior Girls' Shawl Contest (fourteen contestants (split in half); Tia songs off to side)
      Song #1 - warm-up
      Song #2 - contest
      Girls' Fancy (continued on SR10 )
    - Tape 10, August 13, 1983, AFC 1986/038: SR10; RXI 0243; 1 sound tape reel (00:29:08): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Contesting (conclusion)
      Girls' Fancy (continued from SR09; this contest had to be judged over again, as there were ties, and some confusion about the number of judges)
      Song #2 - contest song
      Tiny Tots Male Fancy (one contestant - "automatic champion" - E.J. Snowball?)
      Song #1 - group art [?] outside
      Song #2 - Host Drum
      Junior Boys Fancy (7-12 years; seven contestants)
      Song #1 - "Honey Creek" - warm-up
      Song #2 - Host Drum - Contest
      Junior Boys Fancy (13-17 years)
      Song #1 - Warm-up; Side drum
      Song #2 - Contest; Host Drum
      Intertribal Dance
      Paul Brill Special = Host Drum
    - Tape 11, August 13, 1983, AFC 1986/038: SR11; RXI 0244; 1 sound tape reel (00:32:15): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Speech by Alfred Gilpin, Omaha (about Paul Brill, who helped Omahas on tribal enrollment; Honor Speech for Paul Brill; made family trees for Omaha families)
      Presentation of Family Trees (scroll with ribbons tied around)
      2 Elderly Women
      1 Sister
      Cut-off (needless to record all presentations)
      Warm-up song by Host Drum
      General dance
      Another general dance song by Honey Creek
      Maria danced this one (blended)
      Second general dance by Tia Piah drum group
      Third general dance - host drum
    - Tape 12, August 13, 1983, AFC 1986/038: SR12; RXI 0245; 1 sound tape reel (00:32:14): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      End of third general dance - host drum
      Clown dancers - Honey Creek
      Announcement for Pueblo Butterfly dance (explanation of songs)
      Butterfly Dance - 1
      Check for phasing (else placement of mikes); Carl carried mics around with singers. Praise singer puts down drum.
      Tiny Tot Shawl - Host drum
      Something lost in here while rehooking up to other Nagra
      [untranscribed word] changes hands
      Warm up
      Little Boys Fancy Dance
      Junior Boys Fancy
      Traditional Cloth (Tiny Tots Girls)
    - Tape 13, August 13, 1983, AFC 1986/038: SR13; RXI 0246; 1 sound tape reel (00:32:23): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
    - Tape 14, August 13, 1983, AFC 1986/038: SR14; RXI 0247; 1 sound tape reel (00:22:07): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
    - Paul Brill Special, August 13, 1983, AFC 1986/038: SR85; RYS 3702; 1 sound cassette: analog, 1 7/8 ips
      This may be a dub tape specifically made to include only the Paul Brill Special material. Side 1: Honoring song for Paul Brill. Speech by Alfred Gilpin. Side 2: First few presentations.
    - Tape 15, August 14, 1983, AFC 1986/038: SR15; RXI 0248; 1 sound tape reel (00:33:00): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
    - Tape 16, August 14, 1983, AFC 1986/038: SR16; RXI 0249; 1 sound tape reel (00:32:23): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
    - Tape 17, August 14, 1983, AFC 1986/038: SR17; RXI 0250; 1 sound tape reel (00:32:22): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
    - Tape 18, August 14, 1983, AFC 1986/038: SR18; RXI 0251; 1 sound tape reel (00:32:22): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
    - Tape 19, August 14, 1983, AFC 1986/038: SR19; RXI 0252; 1 sound tape reel (00:32:29): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
    - Tape 20, August 14, 1983, AFC 1986/038: SR20; RXI 0253; 1 sound tape reel (00:32:30): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
    - Tape 21, August 14, 1983, AFC 1986/038: SR21; RXI 0254; 1 sound tape reel (00:32:29): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
    - Tape 22, August 14, 1983, AFC 1986/038: SR22; RXI 0255; 1 sound tape reel (00:32:32): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
    - Tape 23, August 14, 1983, AFC 1986/038: SR23; RXI 0256; 1 sound tape reel (00:32:30): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
    - Tape 24, August 14, 1983, AFC 1986/038: SR24; RXI 0257; 1 sound tape reel (00:32:30): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
    - Tape 25, August 14, 1983, AFC 1986/038: SR25; RXI 0258; 1 sound tape reel (00:32:26): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
    - Tape 26, August 14, 1983, AFC 1986/038: SR26; RXI 0259; 1 sound tape reel (00:32:26): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
    - Tape 27, August 14, 1983, AFC 1986/038: SR27; RXI 0260; 1 sound tape reel (00:32:27): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
    - Tape 28, August 14, 1983, AFC 1986/038: SR28; RXI 0261; 1 sound tape reel (00:32:27): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
    - Tape 29, August 14, 1983, AFC 1986/038: SR29; RXI 0262; 1 sound tape reel (00:32:25): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
    - Tape 30, August 14, 1983, AFC 1986/038: SR30; RXI 0263; 1 sound tape reel (00:10:03): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
- Series 3: 1984 Omaha Tribal Powwow
  Archivist's note: All photos were taken by Dorothy Sara Lee, unless otherwise noted. Her original documentation has been used to describe the content, with minor edits for clarity.
  - Field notes, 1984, 20 pages (Box-folder 1/22)
  - Subseries 1: Photographs
    - Sub-subseries 1: Black-and-white photographs
      - Black-and-white photo logs, 1984, 7 pages (Box-folder 1/18)
      - Camera roll, August 11, 1984, AFC 1986/038: 227546-1; 35 photographs: film, negatives, black and white; 35 mm; Saturday afternoon (Box 1)
        1-6 microphone and cable set-up
        7-9 Charlie Edwards
        10-11 microphone set-up
        12 Host drum
        13-21 Grand Entry
        16-18 Truman Morris, Whipman
        22-25 Powwow Princess
        26 Eagle Feather Presentation
        27 Drum Groups
        28-31 Eagle Feather Special
        29-30 Give-away to Clyde Hallowell
        32-33 Clown
        34-35 Plaques
      - Camera roll, August 11, 1984, AFC 1986/038: 227546-2; 37 photographs: film, negatives, black and white; 35 mm; Saturday afternoon (Box 2)
        1-2 Plaques
        3-5 Presentation to Calvin Tyndall [Sister holding plaque]
        6-10 Consuelo Carmona Presentation
        11-12 Calvin Tyndall and sister Viola
        13 Carmona relatives
        14-15 Japanese tourist
        16-17 Paul Brill and Tyndalls
        18-19 Clown
        20-24 Intertribal
        25-28 Flag lowering and Special
        29-31 Truman Morris - Whipman
        32-33 Unidentified child
        34 Clyde Hallowell
        35 Grand Finale
        36-37 Round dances
      - Camera roll, August 10, 1984, AFC 1986/038: 227546-3; 36 photographs: film, negatives, black and white; 35 mm; Friday afternoon and evening (Box 2)
        2-3 Intertribals
        4-12 Eagle Feather Presentation and Special
        13-17 Round Dances
        18 The Boys
        19-24 Grand Entry
        25 The Boys
        26-33 Eagle Feather Presentation and Special
        34-37 Intertribal
      - Camera roll, August 12, 1984, AFC 1986/038: 227546-4; 32 photographs: film, negatives, black and white; 35 mm; Saturday afternoon (Box 2)
        2-7 Preliminary Hethu'shka Dances
        8-21 Clyde Hallowell Special [18-20: James and Charles Edwards]
        22-24 Tail Dancers Special
        25-26 Grand Entry
        27-29 Eagle Feather Special
        30-34 Flag lowering and Special
      - Camera roll, August 11, 1984, AFC 1986/038: 227546-5; 35 photographs: film, negatives, black and white; 35 mm; Saturday evening (Box 2)
        0-13 Round Dances
        14-16 Contest Judge
        17-26 Eagle Feather Presentation with Hethu'shka Special
        27-34 Child naming and Special
      - Camera roll, August 12-13, 1983, AFC 1986/038: 227861-1; 37 photographs: film, negatives, black and white; 35 mm; Sunday evening; Monday (Box 2)
        1-3 James and Charles Edwards; Dennis Hastings
        4-5 Clyde Hallowell presentation
        7-9 Joe Harlan Special
        10-11 Winnebago Historical Marker
        12 Hole in the Rock
        13-18 Cliffs and Road surrounding Hole in the Rock
        19-23 Missouri River film site
        25-26 Old Mission site
        27-28 Mitchell Family
        29 Blackbird Bend
        30-31 Historical marker about Omaha
        32 Missouri River above Sioux City, Iowa
        33-36 Chief War Eagle monument
      - Black-and-white contact sheets, August 10-13, 1984, 6 photographs: contact sheets, black and white; approx. 8 1/2 in. x 11 in. (Box-folder 1/16)
      - Black-and-white photo prints, August 10-13, 1984, 2 photographs: prints, black and white; various sizes (Box-folder 1/17)
      - Color photo prints, August 10-13, 1984, 6 photographs: prints, color; various sizes (Box-folder 1/19)
    - Sub-subseries 2: Color photographs
      - Color photo logs, 1984, 16 pages (Box-folder 1/20)
      - Camera roll, August 10, 1984, AFC 1986/038: FCP/O84-DSL-1; 20 photographs: color transparencies; 35 mm (slide format); Afternoon/evening (Box 5)
        1-2 Little Girls School
        3-6 Eagle Feather Presentation and Special
        7 Rufus White
        8-15 Round Dances
        16-20 Grand Entry
      - Camera roll, August 10, 1984, AFC 1986/038: FCP/O84-DSL-2; 20 photographs: color transparencies; 35 mm (slide format); Evening (Box 5)
        1-2 Grand Entry
        3 The Boys
        4-6 Tiny Tots
        7-10 Eagle Feather Presentation
        11-20 Intertribal
      - Camera roll, August 10, 1984, AFC 1986/038: FCP/O84-DSL-3; 7 photographs: color transparencies; 35 mm (slide format); Evening (Box 5)
        1-3 Eagle Feather Presentation and Special
        4-7 Combing the hair after mourning
      - Camera roll, August 11, 1984, AFC 1986/038: FCP/O84-DSL-4; 20 photographs: color transparencies; 35 mm (slide format); Afternoon (Box 5)
        1-2 Charlie Edwards
        3-7 Host Drum
        8-20 Grand Entry
      - Camera roll, August 11, 1984, AFC 1986/038: FCP/O84-DSL-5; 20 photographs: color transparencies; 35 mm (slide format); Afternoon (Box 5)
        1-3 End of Grand Entry
        4-6 Tail Dancers
        7-9 Pow-wow Princess Dance
        10-12 Tiny Tots
        13-15 Hethu'shka Dancers
        16-20 Eagle Feather Presentation: Honoring Dance
      - Camera roll, August 11, 1984, AFC 1986/038: FCP/O84-DSL-6; 20 photographs: color transparencies; 35 mm (slide format); Afternoon (Box 5)
        1-2 Eagle Feather Presentation Special
        3 Women behind the drum
        4-5 The Boys
        7-12 Intertribal
        11-12 Japanese dancers
        13-20 Flag lowering and Honoring Song